Never give in. Never give up. Never go back.
Jack Reacher: Never Go Back is a action, thriller,
drama film directed by Edward Zwick.
Years after resigning command of an elite military police unit, the nomadic, righter-of-wrongs Reacher is drawn back
into the life he left behind when his friend and successor, Major Susan Turner is framed for espionage.
Reacher will stop at nothing to prove her innocence and to expose the real
perpetrators behind the killings of his former soldiers.
Jack Reacher, played by Tom Cruise.
Maj. Susan Turner, played by Cobie Smulders.
Samantha Dutton, played by Danika Yarosh.
Capt. Espin, played by Aldis Hodge.
The Hunter, played by Patrick Heusinger.
Sgt. Leach, played by Madalyn Horcher.
Jack Reacher: Never Go Back is a 2016 American action-thriller film directed by Edward Zwick, written by
Richard Wenk, Zwick, and Marshall Herskovitz, and based on the 2013 novel by Lee Child.
A sequel to the 2012 film, the film stars Tom Cruise, reprising
his role as Jack Reacher, and Cobie Smulders.
The plot follows Reacher going on the run with an Army major who has been
framed for espionage, as the two reveal a dark conspiracy.
Principal photography began on October 20, 2015, in New Orleans,
and the film was released on October 21, 2016.
It grossed $162 million worldwide and received mixed reviews from critics, who praised
Cruise's performance and the film's action sequences, but criticized the plot.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, espionage,
military officer, homicide, falsely accused.
The tone is emotional and intense.